<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JakeNTech</title>
    <link>https://jakentech.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JakeNTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 11:44:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jakentech.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The lost macOS Time Machine drive</title>
      <link>https://jakentech.com/blog/macos_timemachine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakentech.com/blog/macos_timemachine/</guid>
      <description>For the last few months, I have been working on a selection of scripts to make going through carved files even easier, you can find the code here. The process of testing these scripts was to carve files from my stash of drives, run the code and fix any errors and move on to the next drive.
Then I found it, not only a drive I haven’t seen since 2019 but one I thought had died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Cooled Hard Drive</title>
      <link>https://jakentech.com/blog/aircooled-harddrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 15:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakentech.com/blog/aircooled-harddrive/</guid>
      <description>Three years ago, I took an intel stock cooler and hot glued it to an old Western Digital 80GB hard drive and created a piece of art. But what data does it hold? Well with nothing else to do it’s time to break out my Forensics VM and USB Write Blocker and have a snoop around.
Just from what I can remember this drive was at some point used as a boot drive in our Family PC and a PC I used to mess about when trying to use various old IDE drives and random PCI cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberStart Elite 2019</title>
      <link>https://jakentech.com/blog/cyberstartelite2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 11:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakentech.com/blog/cyberstartelite2019/</guid>
      <description>At the start of the second year of Cyber Discovery, I was invited to carry on with the program, for what I thought was going to be my last year due to my age. The first year was simply amazing with so many interesting, and frustrating, challenges. Somehow, I even managed to make it to CyberStart Elite in the first year (I still do not know how!).
When CyberStart Game began, I saw that a new base had been added, a forensic one; I began work on this straight away, in the library while at sixth-form on an A1342.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Driving Duck</title>
      <link>https://jakentech.com/blog/alevel-duck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 15:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakentech.com/blog/alevel-duck/</guid>
      <description>Part of the OCR Computer Science A2 is a programming project, which made up a small percentage of the final grade. Our group had a bit of a thing about ducks, I think it’s a deep regret of the teachers telling us about rubber duck decoding and handing us small squeaky ducks. As the start of the project loomed, we had to start brainstorming ideas, my initial idea was a speed limit sign detection AI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>